ANIRUDDH TIWARI



+91 9424669633



aniruddh8022@gmail.com



Ujjain, India



Aniruddh Tiwari



SKILLS

- Programing Language Python, C++, SQL.
- Database Management System MySQL, Firebase, SQlite
- Data Visualization Tools Tableau, Power BI.
- Front End Development HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- UX design Tools Figma, Axure, Adobe XD
- Machine Learning
- **Data Analytics**

EDUCATION

LOKMANYA TILAK VIDHYA VIHAR HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL UJJAIN, INDIA

Class X (2017) Class XII (2019)

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY

Avantika University 2019-2023

PROFILE

My name is Aniruddh Tiwari, and I have been crazy about Machine Learning, Data Science, Data Analytics, and Data Visualization since I was in my 2nd year of academics. I built my first project in Machine Learning, Data Analytics, and Data Visualization in my 3rd year of academics. The feedback from those days from teachers worked wonders. I started learning more about Data Science, Machine learning, and Data Analytics and was amazed to see how little this is explored from a fresh perspective.

EXPERIENCE

UX DEVELOPER INTERN

CJ Digitals 1st June, 2022 - 30 August, 2022

DIGITAL MARKETING INTERN

Anar Business Community App 20th June, 2021 - 20 July, 2021

CERTIFICATION

- Introduction to Data Science (IBM)
- Python Basics for Data Science (IBM)

ACADEMIC PROJECTS

Machine learning Projects

Diabetes Prediction:

Tech Stack: Python, scikit learn, Pandas, NumPy, Matplotlib.

Rate of Intrest Prediction

Tech Stack: Python, scikit learn, Pandas, NumPy, Matplotlib.

Sonar Rock vs Mine Prediction

Tech Stack: Python, scikit learn, Pandas, NumPy, Matplotlib.

Data Analytics Projects:

Business Model:

Created a business model for the running business and identify their problems and create a 5-year business plan.

Coffee Chain Data Visualization Dashboard

Tech Stack: Tableau

Web Application Project

Animal Shelter Hifazat:

Tech Stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, SQL.

Data Base Management System: Mysql

Desktop Application

Animal Shelter Management System:

Tech Stack: Qt c++, Qt Design, SQL **Data Base Management System:** SQLite

Android Mobile Application

Help Us:

Tech Stack: Android Studio, XML, Java **Data Base Management System:** Firebase

RESPONSIBILITY

- Avantika Drama Club Head
- Avantika Designeering Series Content Writer

INTEREST

- Acting
- Writing
- Story telling
- Problem Solving
- Travelling
- Reading